DEVYN HANNA, B.E.S., MS. C.

devynhanna@gmail.com • devynhanna.com • 647-920-3664 • Brampton, Ontario

PROFILE SUMMARY

A highly resourceful and ambitious urban planning graduate with over 10 years of customer service experience and 4 years of management and training experience. Possesses expertise in the field of urban and regional environments in both the United Kingdom and Canadian planning systems. Excellent at collecting, analysing, interpreting, and presenting city planning data and information. Proficient knowledge of Geographical Information Systems and sufficient knowledge of Adobe Photoshop. In possession of strong interpersonal skills which is an asset for both public consultations and working with members of a team.

EDUCATION

Master of Science December 2018

Planning and Regeneration with Distinction

Queens University Belfast, Belfast, Northern Ireland

- Worked on supporting documents for the Belfast City Council on the future regeneration of Castle Street and North Street.
- Provided the Causeway Coast and Glens Borough Council with Coast Regeneration Strategies in preparation for the Portrush 2019 Open.

Honours Bachelor of Environmental Studies

June 2015

Specification in Urban and Regional Environments

York University, Toronto, ON

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Planning Intern

September 2019 – Present

T Johns Consulting Group Ltd., Hamilton, ON

- Conducts policy and zoning research to assist the planning team in the beginnings of development projects.
- Prepares planning justification reports, and supportive evidence for development applications.
- Prepares development applications for zoning and official plan amendments, minor variances, draft plan of condominium and subdivisions, and part lot control applications.
- Assists the planning technician in editing, colouring and updating technical drawings using Bluebeam Software.
- Assists in the organization of public consultations, through event bookings and community outreach programs.
- Organize and prioritize tasks to meet strict deadlines.

 Various administrative tasks completed as needed including filing, updating server files, and delivering applications.

Remote Support Representative

August 2018 – September 2019

Disney Consumer Product & Interactive Media, Kelowna, BC

- Worked alongside a team of support representatives for Disney based programs such as Movies Anywhere and ESPN+
- Responsible for providing exceptional Disney experiences by being the main point of contact for users; turning each interaction over phone, email or live chat into a meaningful connection with guests.
- Ranked among the top communication respondents of the support team.
- Responsible for day-to-day communications over Slack, Salesforce, Zendesk and Outlook. The role
 also includes extensive use of the Microsoft Office Suite.

Le Cellier Signature Dining Server

March 2016 – April 2017

Walt Disney World Resort, Florida, USA

- Participant in the Cultural Representative Program; a one-year contract to work in Epcot in the Canada Pavilion sharing Canadian culture.
- Trained in the Disney Signature Dining Standards which aided in extensive food and wine knowledge.
- Responsible for training new cast members in dining standards.

Assistant Manager

March 2010 - March 2016

Cineplex Entertainment, Brampton, ON

- Part of the management team for both Guest Service and Food Services at the cinema.
- Largely responsible for guest satisfaction and recovery.
- Responsible for the distribution of daily cast member duties, cinema stock ordering, and daily cash flow via Cash Desk.
- Role included extensive use of Microsoft Office Suite, Infor and ADP for maintaining administrative duties, such as scheduling, payroll, and accounts payable.

ASSOCIATIONS

Ontario Professional Planners Institute

Student Member – 2018 – Present